{
    "subject": "resource/Pressmart",
    "predicate": "ontology/location",
    "object": "resource/Hyderabad",
    "human_readable": "Pressmart is located in Hyderabad.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8481597900390625,
            "question": "Where is Pressmart located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7752025127410889,
            "question": "What state is Pressmart located in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6841411590576172,
            "question": "What is the geographical location of Pressmart?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6097696423530579,
            "question": "In which Indian city can you find Pressmart?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6083029508590698,
            "question": "Is Pressmart situated in a metropolitan area?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48928046226501465,
            "question": "What is the name of the city where Pressmart operates?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47871100902557373,
            "question": "What region of India does Pressmart belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46087387204170227,
            "question": "What city is home to Pressmart?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38442665338516235,
            "question": "Would you find Pressmart in a rural or urban setting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.15868456661701202,
            "question": "Is Hyderabad known for its technological industry?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Pressmart is located in Hyderabad.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7407_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Would you find Pressmart in a rural or urban setting?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7407_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What city is home to Pressmart?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7407_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What region of India does Pressmart belong to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7407_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7407_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7407_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7407_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7407_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7407_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7407_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7407_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7407_90.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7407_93.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7407_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents clearly mention that Pressmart Media Limited and Pressmart are based out of Hyderabad, Andhra Pradesh. Therefore, the statement \"Pressmart is located in Hyderabad\" is supported by the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}